Hi, I'm probiotics, and I can't do anything when parasites are already living inside you
eating your food.
Hi, I'm a juice cleanse, and all I do is flood your body with sugar while the parasites
inside you keep feeding.
Hi, I'm fiber supplements, and all I do is pile more bulk on top of a gut that's already
clogged and backed up.
Hi, I'm detox tea, and all I do is make you pee more while the real problem stays stuck
inside your colon.
Hi, I'm laxatives, and all I do is force everything out temporarily while the parasites
and build up stay exactly where they are.
Hi, I'm Soursop Bitters, and all of these won't do anything until you flush out what's
actually living inside your gut.
I have 15 African herbs that kill parasites, break down toxic buildup, and flush out pounds
of waste that's been sitting in your colon for years.
Probiotics can't colonize a dirty gut.
Fiber can't push through a blocked colon.
Detox teas can't kill what's feeding off your food.
But I can, because I clean the gut first, then flush the toxins out.
People don't really like my bitter taste, but that's because real gut cleanses don't
come sweetened with fillers.
They come raw in their purest form.
They love me because their bloating finally disappears.
Their energy comes back, and they stop wasting money on things that never worked.
They just needed to flush first.
(splashing)
Whew!